since the times of Ancient Rome there was such a
ещё со времён Древнего Рима был такой
principle Yes, that a slave is not
принцип Да что раб не несёт
responsible for the affairs of his
ответственности за дела своего
master Alice continue, I’m from the city of
хозяина Алиса продолжай я из города
Khmelnitsk You’re from We’re from Russia, I
Хмельницке Вы откуда Мы из России я
understand, let’s talk normally Come on, come
понял давайте поговорим нормально Давай
on Alice
давай давай Алиса
stop How are you, conductor Kato I’m from
стоп Как дела у вас дирижёр Като Я из
the city of Khmelnitsk You  where we are from Russia, the
города Хмельницке Вы откуда Мы из России
city of Smolensk, what an interesting city it would be
город Смоленск город какой интересный бы
Smolensk Smolensk and the World Cup are communicating
Смоленск Смоленск а ЧМ общаетесь
here I don’t know we want to talk to you nouveau
тут не знаю хочем поговорить с вами нува
not about war or
не о войне и не
politics How are you doing Wait I’m talking let’s
политике Как у вас дела Подожди я говорю
not About Vaughn or about politics Okay well
давайте не О воне ни о политике Окей ну
no problem for us just now  I got
без проблем нам просто сейчас попался
one like that, let someone not in the frame
один такой давай Пусть кто не в кадре не
speak. It turns out that I’ll just
говорит Балаган получается я просто
switch it. Let’s see you in the frame and
переключу Давайте Вот вы в кадре вы
then you speak. Let him not scream
тогда и говорите Пусть он не кричит
from the side, there is someone from the side screaming without any problems,
сбоку там кто сбоку кричит без проблем
just a microphone, I’ll just look, I’ll say right away
просто микрофон я просто смотрите сразу
that
скажу да что
we don’t have anything to do with you  to ordinary Russians
мы не имеем к вам простым россиянам
We understand no complaints, don’t
Никаких претензий мы понимаем ите не
look at us Many don’t understand, but I
смотри у нас Многие не понимают но я
preach this thesis among Ukrainians
проповедуют среди украинцев вот эту тези
that, as it were, you, ordinary people,
что как бы вот ещё ж с вы ж простые люди
nothing depends on you Truth Well, Putin
от вас ничего не зависит Правда Ну Путин
attacked, he decided since the times of Ancient
напал он решил ещё со времён Древнего
Rome  such a principle Yes, that a slave
Рима был такой принцип Да что раб не
is not responsible for the affairs of his
несёт ответственности за дела своего
master, that is, therefore, we cannot
хозяина то есть Поэтому мы не можем вас
blame you for anything. If you somehow influenced
обвинять в чём-то Если вы как-то влияли
Yes, there was a president who you
Да на вас был президент который вы
elect, would you influence him, then we would have
избирает влияли бы на него да то мы бы к
something for you -  then they had a claim And if you are
вам что-то имели претензию А если вы
slaves in this country, conquered
рабы в этой стране покорённый
Well, in short, you have a good policy And
Ну короче у тебя хорошая политика А
why are you sitting in front of the flag of
почему ты сидишь на фоне флага
Ukraine And why are you sitting in front of the flag of
Украины А почему ты на фоне флага
Ukraine Well, it’s clear that you are in this
Украины сидишь Ну понятно что ты в этой
country Why so directly propagandize
стране Зачем так прямо пропагандировать
that you are in this growing country  you live And why am I
что ты в этой рос стране живёшь А чем
stressing you out, and with the trident it’s
тебя напрягаю я ещё и с тризубом ту нем
just interesting, I like it, I
просто интересном мне нравится мне
like sitting against the background of the flag, so I
нравится сидеть на фоне флага вот я
get a kick out of it, but you’re sitting against the background of
кайфую от этого вот ты же сидишь на фоне
the curtains. I’m not saying that I sat there against the background.
штор Я же не говорю что там села на фоне
What, well, these are slightly different things  Well, how a
Что Да ну это немного разные вещи Ну как
little different everyone sits, so I
немного разные каждый сидит вот я же
don’t tell you that you have a neckline there
тебе не Преда что у тебя там вырез такой
or not, everyone sits with whatever they want and
или не такой каждый с чем хочет тем и
sits the question Why does this bother you? Yes, I’m
сидит вопрос Почему тебя это тревожит Да
just interested. It doesn’t matter to me.
мне просто интересно Меня это никак не
That’s why you’re interested in
Вот почему тебя заинтересовал именно
the flag. I’m not interested.  flag of Ukraine
флаг Меня заинтересовал не флаг Украины
And the fact that you are sitting against the background of the flag
А то что ты на фоне флага сидишь
Correct Because if I put
Правильно Потому что если я поставил
Why did I put a flag behind me yes yes
Почему я поставил сзади себя флаг да да
Because if I put a flag in front
Потому что если бы я поставил спереди
of me you wouldn’t
себя флаг ты бы меня не
see me that Well it’s logical Well what are your
видела что Ну логично Ну какие у тебя
hobbies Do you
хобби есть
play chess well  a little hello, how
шахматы хорошо играешь немножко алло как
long ago, from the fourth grade
давно с четвёртого класса
professionally to the eleventh grade
профессионально по одиннадцатый класс
Then I no longer played seriously
Потом больше уже не играл серьёзно
well,
хорошо
but whatever you want in chat roulette
а сам что хочешь в чат рулетки
conversations, I wish
разговоров бы
I had
я
research
исследовательские у меня
motives, it’s just that in fact it
мотивы просто на самом деле меня это
surprised me that you so openly
удивило то что ты прям открыто
expressed your position on  that
так высказал свою позицию по поводу что
you don’t have any aggression towards
у тебя нет никакой агрессии к
us
нам
Swami Neli influence they
Свами на Нели повлиять они бесправные
were powerless slaves and there were no claims against them
рабы были и к ним Никаких претензий не
That is, if there were
было То есть если было каких-то
two slave owners quarreling with each other,
два рабовладельца с собой ссорятся да у
they have claims against each other But not against
них претензии друг к другу Но не к рабам
each other’s slaves you
друг друга понимаешь
just understand  world
просто мир
evo Yes, feudalism passed there and now there
эво Да прошли там феодальные и сейчас
are different systems. Well, most of the
вот разные строи Ну вот большинство
countries are democratic. We, for example, in
стран они демократические Мы например в
Ukraine, we elected one president there, we
Украине мы выбрали там одного президента
don’t like it, we chose a second one, then
не понравится выбрали второго потом
a third And so on. Yes, we understand that
третьего И так дальше Да мы понимаем что
you are in your own country. Yes, you were born, you
вы в своей стране Да вы родились вы её
did not choose it.  Yes, you didn’t choose to be born
не выбирали Да вы не не выбрали родиться
a slave, there was no such thing as what you say God
рабом не было такого что вы говорите Бог
send me here I want to be shorter Here,
пошли меня сюда Я хочу короче быть Вот
here in this country there was no such thing as being powerless in this country. It’s true.
тут бесправным в этой стране не было
How do you feel about people
правда А как ты относишься к людям вот
from Ukraine who, well, they vehemently hate
из Украины которые Ну яро прям ненавидят
both the common people and  in general, military
и простой народ и в целом военных
Russians
русских
who Well, attacked
которые Ну напали на
Ukraine, not at all, that is, it
Украину не совсем не по то есть
surprises you Why do people hate the
тебя удивляет Почему люди ненавидят
Russian military no, it surprises me, it
российских военных нет меня удивляет
doesn’t even surprise me I’m just wondering
даже не удивляет Я просто интересуюсь
how you feel about them
как ты к ним
Ukrainians who vehemently hate Russians,
украинцам которые яро ненавидят русских
ordinary Russians Russians or military people, you
простых русских Русских или военных ты
talk to  don’t screw up the military Well, with the military,
говори ты с военных не сри Ну с военными
everything is definitely the military must be killed And that’s it,
всё однозначно военных надо убить И всё
so that they Who will die, who will run away
да чтобы они Кто умрёт кто убежит потому
because they attacked our country is absolutely
что они напали на нашу страну абсолютно
normal, everyone who hates the Russian
нормально все кто ненавидит российских
military is handsome, yes, but everyone who
военных красавчики да но все кто
hates Russian slaves Yes,
ненавидит рабов российских Да вот
those who don’t, but just here they are  the slaves of the
которые нет а просто вот они рабы
Russian Federation do not understand, I will
Российской Федерации на не понимают я
sing among the Ukrainians. This is the thesis that there is
пропою среди украинцев Вот это тезис что
no need for aggression towards slaves, that is,
не нужно агрессии к рабам так то есть
slaves do not decide anything. Well, they
рабы они ничего не решают Ну и они не
cannot influence anything. Yes, you are
могут повлиять ни на что Да ты
aggressive;
агрессирует
he only has his own chains. And that’s
сделать у него свои цепи есть только И
all.  there is to the military Yes, he is aggressive
всё да то есть к военным Да агрессирует
towards slaves People like you Well, what kind of claims can there be,
к рабам Таких как вы Ну какие могут быть
just not everyone understands everyone
претензии просто не все понимают все
in our Ukraine, many people think that
думают у нас в Украине Многие думают что
you in Russia also live in our society and you are
вы в России тоже жите вмо обществе и вы
responsible for this war, you elected
ответственны за эту войну вы избирали
your president, your government,
вашего президента ваше правительство
for example,
например да
yes.  wait now we have a small rearrangement
Вот подожди сейчас у нас перестановка
Now for
Сейчас
a second
секунду
all our asses are on fire now now
всё задницы пригорели сейчас сейчас
wait
подожди
[music] I
[музыка]
’ll sit down [ __ ]
присяду [__]
not a monitor Well yes It’s
не монитор А ну да
logical
Логично
[ __ ] in your mouth well put it yourself [ __ ] T
[__] [__] в рот ну сам поставь [__] Т
move over I’m not moving just
подвинься не не пересаживаю просто
see everything is
пови всё
almost ready That is, you consider Russian people to be
почти То есть ты считаешь русских людей
slaves  so No, well, you said that we are not
рабами так Нет ну ты сказал то что мы не
to blame for the fact that we were born in Russia,
виноваты в том что мы родились в России
that
то что
Look, I consider Rami those people on
Смотри я считаю Рами тех людей от
whom nothing depends in their country,
которых ничего не зависит в ихней стране
who are ruled by Noni, who control their
которыми управляют Нони управляют своей
power, I asked you, are you
властью я теб спросил Вы вы на что-то
influencing something in  to this country you said
влияете в этой стране вы сказали
no, you consider yourself
нет это вы себя считаете
slaves That is, it turns out you are also a slave
рабами То есть получается ты тоже раб
No why in my country I decide, I
Нет почему я в своей стране решаю я
elect, I influence the authorities, the authorities
избирают я влияю на власть власть
act on my
действует от моего
behalf, here we just have problems with sound
имени тут просто со звуком у нас
and you are from the microphone Stand up and you
проблемы а ты с микрофона Встань во всё
can repeat everything  I ask once yes yes
можешь повторить прошу раз раз да да Всё
Everything is fine ska get up from the microphone and everything
всё хорошо ска встань с микрофона и всё
has become
стало
fine Yes I seem to be sitting
хорошо Да я вроде и так сижу
fine Repeat please I couldn’t hear
нормально Повтори пожалуйста не слышно
Thea repeat
было тея
What should I repeat Well here’s my last
повт Что тебе повторить Ну вот последний
last sentence I can’t remember
последнее своё предложение послед не пом
my last sentence this is why
сво послед предложение это почему
with Russian slaves  let's start from the beginning, I
с русских рабами давай начнём сначала я
don't consider Russians to be slaves. I think that I
не считаю русских рабами Я считаю вот я
consider people to be those whose
людей считаю тех которые ничего от них
state does not depend on them, I consider them to be
не зависит их государство их считаю
slaves, that is, they are controlled and they do not
рабами то есть ими управляют а они не
elect power. I asked you, yes, with a
избирают власть я у тебя спросил да с
girl, or are you deciding something in your
девушкой или вы что-то решаете в своей
you said no to the country, well, that is, you are slaves,
стране вы сказали нет ну то есть вы рабы
you recognized yourself as such, not me. I don’t
вы себя такими признали а не я Я же не
know your point of view, for example, I
знаю твоя точка зрения я вот например
don’t consider myself a slave, wait, let’s say something
себя не считаю рабом подожди давай так
in your country depends on you, yes, that is, that
от тебя что-то в твоей стране
is, it turns out, uh  you are to
м да то есть то есть получается э ты ты
blame for the fact that Russia attacked
виноват в том что Россия напала на
Ukraine Well, at that moment, no, wait
Украину Ну на тот момент нет подожди ещё
again Look, you’re asking Does something depend on
раз Смотри ты спрашиваешь Зависит ли от
me now in my country
меня сейчас в моей стране что-то не
?
Россия напала на Украину Да она от
works or not no And that
твоего имени действует или нет нет А то
is, you don’t control the president
есть ты не управляешь президентом
No I don’t control the president doesn’t
Нет не управляю президент тебя не
represent you no everything So you’re a slave yes
представляет нет всё Значит ты раб да ты
you admit it but it turns out you’re a
ты это признаёшь а получается ты тоже
slave too No why Come on ask me
раб Нет почему Давай спрашивай меня
Similarly you represent you
Аналогично ты представля ты
represent the interests of your country Yes the
представляешь интересы своей страны Да
president represents mine  I
президент представляет мои интересы я
delegate interests to him in the elections Yes, and like
ему делегирую на выборах Да и как и
other people, we are the people who are the
другие люди мы народ который есть
source of power, we delegate to the president,
источник власти мы делегирую президенту
we delegate to deputies, we delegate to the
мы делегирую депутатам мы делегирую
local council Yes, their powers and they
местным советом Да свои полномочия и они
act on our behalf on behalf of the
выступают от нашего имени от имени
people of
народа
Ukraine, President President Zelensky Yes,
Украины президент президент Зеленский Да
all decisions come from  on behalf of the people of
все решения они идут от имени народа
Ukraine, it’s not just Zelensky himself, but
Украины не просто вот Зеленский себе Да
on what behalf does he act on behalf of the
от чего имени он действует от имени
people of Ukraine? I bear responsibility for
народа Украины Я несу ответственность за
all his decisions. I bear the decision for
все его решение Я несу решение за
Poroshenko’s responsibility for
ответственности Порошенко за
Yanukovych’s responsibility. And so
ответственности Януковича решение И так
on for all the presidents because I am a
дальше за всех президентов потому что я
citizen, I am
гражданин я
elected to them.  who is the president?
избирают им что та кто такой президент
This is the man whom we all appointed Yes,
Это человек которого мы все поставили Да
so that he carries out our
чтоб он исполнял нашу
will, we delegate him this right for
волю мы ему делегировать дали это право
5 years there, it depends on us and we
на там 5 лет от нас это зависит и мы
decide to take him or not to take him,
решаем забрать его или не забрать
leave or take
оставить или взять
another If you don’t decide anything, then you are
другого Если вы не решаете ничего то вы
slaves,
рабы
we  not
мы не
fish Well, this is an interesting position
рыб Ну это интересная позиция на самом
actually Well it
деле Ну так и
is Well look What is the
есть Ну смотри В чём
essence of democracy and slavery Yes in
суть демократии и вот рабства Да в
democracy people
демократии люди
elect power Yes they authorize them
избирают власть Да они уполномочиваю там
for 5 years so we give you such and such
на 5 лет вот мы Вам даём такие такие-то
powers Yes they control the power and so
полномочия Да контролируют власть и так
on  in slaveholding it turns out that
дальше в рабовладельческом получается у
Vato
вато
has someone in power, no one
есть кто-то Во власти его никто не
elects him, no one appoints him, he is
избирает его никто не назначает он
not respected by anyone Yes, but he can
никому не почтен Да а он может над вами
do whatever he wants over you, collect tribute from you
что угодно делать собирать с вас
in the form of taxes,
Дань в виде налогов
and throw you somewhere else for slaughter in
Да кидать вас куда-то там на убой в
another  country and do anything at all,
другую страну и что угодно вообще делать
you won’t do anything to him, just
вы ему ничего не сделаете вот просто
nothing. For example, we had a president
ничего У нас например был президент
who decided to try to
такой который решил попробовать
play around with dictatorship. Yanukovych ran away to
поиграться в диктатуру Янукович убежал к
you because we said no, we are not slaves,
Вам потому что мы сказали нет мы не рабы
we won’t tolerate such an
мы не будем се терпеть такого
attitude, we can’t go out and  beat
отношения у нас нельзя выходить и бить
people at rallies, disperse them because we
людей на митинги разгонять потому что мы
are the source of power in our country Yes,
есть источником власти в нашей стране Да
we have the right to gather for peaceful
мы имеем право собираться на мирные
demonstrations to demand something Yes, uh,
демонстрации требовать что-то Да ээ
put pressure on the authorities to make
давить на власть для про принятие
or cancel some decisions
каких-то или отмену каких-то решений
because we are the
потому что мы
People, well, it turns out you  you hate the
Народ ну получается ты ненавидишь
Russians who Slava voted for
россиян которые Слава э голосовали За
Putin there I don’t know at all in general they
Путина там я не знаю вообще в целом за
voted for someone So I hate
кого-то голосовали Итак я ненавижу
the Russians who say that yes it
россиян которые говорят что да типа
turns out I’m responsible for this
получается Я несу ответственность за это
for the actions of my government I support and
за действия моей власти Я поддерживаю и
so on Yes if you say that you  you don’t
так дальше Да если ты говоришь что ты не
bear any responsibility Yes,
несёшь никакой ответственности Да от
nothing depends on you, then you, you, uh,
тебя ничего не зависит то ты ты ээ не
are not a person who expresses his will
есть человек который выражает свою волю
Yes, you are a slave of this system, this president,
Да ты раб этой системы этого президента
or whatever you call him, the king. I
или как он у вас там называется царь Я
don’t know the emperor, anyone, yes, that is,
не знаю император кто угодно да то есть
to you. Well, who can  to have any
к тебе Ну какие могут быть к тебе
complaints against you Well, it doesn’t work out against me
претензии Ну ко мне никаких получается
Well, that’s why I’m saying that’s why It’s just that
Ну то есть я же говорю поэтому Просто у
many of us in Ukraine put an
нас многие в Украине они ставят знак
equal sign to all Russians, so they
равенства ко всем россиянам так они
think that you are free. It’s just that here in
думают что вы свободные Просто у нас в
Ukraine everyone is used to it. Yes, we are free
Украине все привыкли Да что Мы свободные
people and it’s difficult for us  understand that somewhere in
люди и нам сложно понять что где-то в
another country it may be different and
другой стране может быть по-другому и
that’s why When you go to chat roulette
поэтому Когда вы выходите в чат рулетку
Why do they all yell at you? Because
Почему на вас Орут все да Потому что
people think that you live free in a
люди думают что вы свободные живёте в
Democratic country and this war depends on you
Демократической стране и от вас зависит
and that’s why they yell at you
эта война и поэтому на вас ругаются есть
right away I recommend making a sign
вот сразу Я рекомендую сделать табличку
and right away nothing depends on me
да сразу такую от меня ничего не зависит
and immediately show it and Booth will
и сразу показывать и Бут спокойно
react calmly first they will start,
реагировать сначала начнут стартовать
then they explained that the people
потом объяснили что народ от меня ничего
in this country do not depend on me I am a person without rights
в этой стране не зависит Я бесправный
here Well that’s
здесь человек Ну и
all Well, in general, how do you think
всё Ну вообще как думаете чем закончится
the war will end  operation How will the military
военная операция Чем закончится военная
operation end with the defeat of the Russian Federation by
операция поражением Российской Федерации
dividing it into a
разделением её на
dozen different states on a
ээ десяток разных государств по
national basis on a
национальному признаку по
territorial basis and the liberation of the
территориальному признаку и освобождение
people of the Russian Federation from this
народа Российской Федерации от этого
slave
рабского
yoke, it will be clear that
ярма ва понятно
special training programs will
специальные обучающие программы будут
teach people how to elect how to
людей учить Как нужно избирать как можно
monitor the actions of the authorities then as
мониторить действия власти потом как
possible  Let’s say that the authorities require accountability,
можно скажем отчётность власти требовать
that is, they will teach Well, this
так то есть будут учить Ну это
will be a transitional period from
переходной такой будет период от
dictatorship to democracy, first there
диктатуры к демократии сначала нужно
will be a need for a population that did not know how
будет ну население которое не знало как
to live freely. Yes, they will need to be
это жить свободно Да ему нужно будет
shown what mechanisms there are in a
показывать какие есть механизмы в
free state. Yes, for example,
свободном государстве Да например
demonstration rallies, for example, will
митинги демонстрации вот например будут
come  people from France There from Ukraine
приезжать люди из Франции Там с Украины
from England say Look here,
с Англии сказать Вот смотрите у нас
for example,
например
if you don’t like macron’s actions there Yes
если не нравятся там действия макрона Да
People come out for example To a rally yes To a
Люди выходят например На митинг да На
rally to a demonstration and that’s normal
митинг на демонстрацию и это нормально с
Boris Johnson will come from Britain there to
Британии приедет Борис Джонсон там по
tell you a lecture there about how
рассказывает вам лекцию там о том как
people can  influence this order, how does this
люди могут влиять на э уряд как это
impact the government? Yes, we're a traveler. I
проки на правительство Да мы едук Я
can come, which city is yours,
может приеду вот у вас какой
from which city?
с какого города со Смоленска со
methods of influencing
лекции в Смоленске Да методы влияния на
local authorities For example, I have experience Yes,
местную власть Например у меня есть опыт
we will teach different companies at the level of our city everything is fine, the main thing is
города научим всё нормально главно
to defeat this hydra of the announcer
победить вот эту гидру дикторскую
and we will quarrel Well, let’s enjoy it
итро будем ссориться Ну давай
I love to
да кайф Я люблю такие
write about such conversations Like it and
разговоры пишиться Поставьте лайк
leave a comment for this obvyazkovo so that this
залиште комент це обовязково чтоб це
video will be more interesting and  more than people Yes,
видео побачить бильше и бильше людей Да
we’re sorry, don’t worry about why you
мы повинни доно что ты такие
got high on such thoughts Yes,
думки кайфанул
damn, well, I’m amazed at the dude, my
Да блин ну всё чуваку бесю дивиться моя
position is like this Yes, who from Russia is
позиция такая Да кто нас из России
listening to us, why do they say that’s a mouse,
слушает ну почему они говорят вот мышь
it doesn’t depend on me, it doesn’t depend on me,
это от меня не зависит от меня не
but if it doesn’t depend on you, then you  slave You have to
да если от тебя не зависит то ты раб Ты
understand this for yourself,
должен для себя это понять от тебя
nothing depends on you. That is, you are a person without
ничего не зависит То есть ты человек без
rights. And if something depends on you,
пра А если от тебя что-то зависит да
then it means they are yelling at you
тогда значит на тебя получается орут
rightfully. Yes, and swearing at you, write on th
правомерно Да и матюка тебя пись на й
Telegram directly at the same time axis VN
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse duzhe and  very respectfully YouTube has taken
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg ODS in your ban and so
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
much video I don’t show people every now and then I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for this
показуе информация про стримы тому для
purpose for Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
to write directly at once and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram okrim video also tezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим вдео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we  blame you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati
тримати
postiyny operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write Ne
пиши Ne